you know there's a difference between being focused and being caught up and um one thing
that i've learned from i'm covering this because i have a hive right here but one thing i've learned
from being in the entertainment business and then like looking at politics and then activism is that
you have the same people in every place you have people who are genuinely just about the cause
and you have people who are climbers and you have people who are positioned
and you can be positioned and understand your position but then sometimes you have people who
are positioned and they start to think that their position is about them being somehow
dominant it's the it to me it's the difference between when something goes from feeling like
divinity like it's divine to now it's dominant and we see this in how people become dictators right we
see this in how people become cult leaders they start to see themselves beyond their morale mortality
and their morality and it's something i've had to become a lot more conscious of as i see myself
being more involved in advocacy and something i have to make sure that i do not fall into because
i can see how it's easy to fall into because you get sycophants around you and you get people who
really are just like no we need a leader we need a leader we need a leader and it's like i think the
only way that you really save yourself from that is by always encouraging everybody else to be their own
leaders the only way that you really um demonstrate a commitment to not being that is by making sure
that your leadership is about bringing people to recognize their own leadership i'm telling you what
i love about seeing these students in their their encampments is that you're not seeing a single
person you're seeing people who are all seeing the importance of their individual involvement
as a part of a collective and you don't see followers you see a collective and when i start
looking at people who are like building followers i say to myself hmm and i hate when people try and
assign that to me because that's not what i'm about i am about bringing information to people and
existing in my own love of self as a way to encourage people to exist in their own love of self
i don't love myself more than you should love yourself we have to build leadership with each
other we have to be able to identify the unique ways in which each of us can be leaders in our own
lives and how that informs the way that we are leaders in our social existence and i encourage all of you to
ask yourself today what way am i a leader what do i bring in leadership have a good day
and drop it in the comments to get more messages like this every morning you can follow my patreon
where we start every day with morning musings to get our mind right our heart right so we can walk
right go to the link in bio amanda seals on patreon
you